(Penny:)So, how do you want me
to cut it?
(Sheldon:)How about Bill Gates
meets Nikola Tesla?
(Leonard:)So, business in the front,
science in the back.
(Penny:)Or I don't cut it and
maybe just style it a little.
(Sheldon:)I'm in your hands.
(Sheldon:)Do a good job and I'll tell you
Cosmo's ten dynamite tips
(Sheldon:)to enjoy your PMS.
(Penny:)Can you keep him quiet?
(Penny:)Maybe jangle some keys
in front of him?
That doesn't work anymore.
(Leonard:)He just thinks I'm taking him
to the doctor.
(Leonard:)So, now that you're
no longer invested in string theory,
(Leonard:)what are you gonna pursue?
(Sheldon:)There are so
(Sheldon:)black holes, dark matter...
(Penny:)Leonard was telling me
about dark matter,
(Penny:)but I didn't really understand it.
(Sheldon:)Don't feel bad.
Neither does he.
(Sheldon:)OK...
(Penny:)...what do you think?
Have you evr even seen
a picture of Tesla?